

Angelo F. Macapinlac Software Developer

(+63) 9174428840 (Viber) | angelofresnoza@yahoo.com.ph

Professional C# .NET Web Developer with 5 years continuing experience. Expert in .NET Framework and .NET Core technology Web App development using MVC architectural pattern and RESTful Web API development. Achieving to be a successful full-stack developer.

Experience

5 years of total experience

Mar 2022 - Present C# .NET Developer (Contract)

CTBC Bank (Philippines) Corp | National Capital Reg, Philippines

Industry Banking / Financial Services
Specialization IT/Computer - Software

Role Software Engineer/Programmer

Mar 2022 - Present C# .NET Developer

H2 Software Consulting Services, Inc | National Capital Reg, Philippines

Industry Computer / Information Technology (Software)

Specialization IT/Computer - Software

Role Software Engineer/Programmer

Apr 2019 – Mar 2022 **Software Developer**

Amellar Solutions | National Capital Reg, Philippines

Industry Computer / Information Technology (Software)

Specialization IT/Computer - Software

Role Software Engineer/Programmer

Aug 2017 - Apr 2019 Data and Technology Support

Amellar Solutions | National Capital Reg, Philippines

Industry Computer / Information Technology (Software)

Specialization IT/Computer - Software
Role Software and Data Support

Education

2013 - 2017

Technological University of the Philippines

Bachelor's/College Degree in Information System | Philippines

Technical Skills

Advanced

Software Development, Web Development, C#, Visual Studio, ASP.NET Core, Oracle SQL, SQL Server, Web Development, REST API, OOP

Personal Skills

- Excellent written and verbal communication skills in both English and Filipino.
- Ability to work independently or as part of a team
- Ability to focus on a task and adapt quickly